I don't want you to think, to get an impression that Feng Shui is all about the rules and about the elements.
So what you also got to do, you have to feel the energy there.
What kind of energy is in the room?
So if, for example, if there is clutter in the room, the energy is definitely not good enough.
It's too ying so it's stagnant.
You want to clear that clutter.
So if there is certain like heavy piece of furniture, or piece of furniture that you don't like is in the southeast, that's not, not going to give you a very good, supportive energy also.
So another thing that you, you want to look, you want to see, do you use the room often enough?
Even if it's a beautiful room but you don't use it often enough, so the energy becomes stagnant.
So what you want to do is to move the energy.
You want to play some music, burn some candles, open the windows once in a while to let that fresh chi come in.
So this way you create a movement of energy in the area and this way energy does, is not stagnant.